<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Unity on 識之箱庭</title><link>https://HoshikawaRyuukou.github.io/tags/unity/</link><description>Recent content in Unity on 識之箱庭</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-tw</language><copyright>HoshikawaRyuukou</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 21:11:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://HoshikawaRyuukou.github.io/tags/unity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Unity - Sites</title><link>https://HoshikawaRyuukou.github.io/posts/unity-sites/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 21:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://HoshikawaRyuukou.github.io/posts/unity-sites/</guid><description>Blog 游戏石匠Super L&amp;rsquo;s Blog コガネブログ 渋谷ほととぎす通信 きゅぶろぐ LIGHT11 Raspberlyのブログ PG日誌 やらなイカ？ Game Dev Beginner - Everyone Can Make Games LianBai Learning Unity Learning Materials</description></item><item><title>Unity - 筆記</title><link>https://HoshikawaRyuukou.github.io/posts/unity-%E7%AD%86%E8%A8%98/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 21:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://HoshikawaRyuukou.github.io/posts/unity-%E7%AD%86%E8%A8%98/</guid><description>Analysis Unity Optimize Your Game Using Profiler Unity 手機遊戲最佳化雜談– 內建Profiling Audio Unity Audio Clip Import Settings For The Best Performance Audio tutorial for Unity: the Audio Mixer The right way to make a volume slider in Unity Build repositories.cfg could not be loaded. unity Camera Understanding Orthographic Size 探寻 Unity Camera 属性之 Clear Flags Unityの画面のアスペクト比と解像度を自動変換　全スマホ・複数解像度に対応させる Editor 在unity编辑器不同位置添加菜单 SerializeReferenceをつけている型をリネーム・削除する時の注意点 What are EditorBuildSettings config objects used for or how can I use them?</description></item><item><title>Unity - Packages</title><link>https://HoshikawaRyuukou.github.io/posts/unity-packages/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 21:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://HoshikawaRyuukou.github.io/posts/unity-packages/</guid><description>Package Manager Installing Packages using UPM Package manager -&amp;gt; Advanced project settings Add Scoped Registries Name: package.openupm.com URL: https://package.openupm.com Scope(s): com.cysharp.unitask Package manager -&amp;gt; Packages: My Registries -&amp;gt; Install Unity中 .asmdef文件的作用 使用OpenUPM发布自己的Unity项目 开发Unity PackageManager 插件包 Creating Custom Packages for Unity 2018.3 How to remodel your project for asmdef and UPM Animation DOTween Link Async UniTask openupm - com.cysharp.unitask Patterns &amp;amp; Practices for efficiently handling C# async/await cancel processing and timeouts 精选Unity-Github开源库分享 最完美的异步操作解决方案 UniTask C# Task 指南 async/await,disposableを使って素直で読みやすいコードを書く UniTaskCompletionSource Should Support CancellationToken Debug UnityIngameDebugConsole Dependency Injection VContainer openupm - jp.</description></item></channel></rss>